Welcome to Am I Tripping? [music] You be
the judge. Where the hot takes are
unfiltered. Just like the ones you send
in your group chat or post on your
burner account. [music]
>> No rage bait, just raw opinions.
>> We listen, we judge, but you are the
jury presiding over the court. Sister
judges Reesei Colbert and Season
Williams. Court is in session. Isa Ray
tripping for kicking Amanda Seals out
the insecure crew. Where your kids at?
And he went and he's nuts. I ain't gonna
say that you emotional and you
sensitive. You need to suck it up and
get over it. I didn't say all [laughter]
that.
>> Hey, season.
>> Hi, Reesei. Court is in session and
we're going to kick things off like we
always do with Culture Court. Culture
Court is where we take stories from
viral to verdicts. The first case on the
docket in culture court this week is a
case that we're calling insecure kicked
out the crew. [laughter] Now, rather
than getting into a long Toronto
explanation, let's just take a look at
the video that I think will explain what
we mean.
>> Hey, do you want to go on tour?
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> Look, we're It's high. It's a It's
insecure. Insecure.
>> But we're very secure now.
>> We're very secure. It's always very
>> Come see us [music] on tour.
>> Okay. Now I saw four people in there. I
saw Jay Ellis. I saw Issa. I saw Natasha
Rothwell. And I saw Ivon Origy. Who did
you think was missing from that lineup?
>> I didn't see Amanda SS. I thought she
was part of the crew. What What
happened? Where we going? What's going
on?
>> So I think that the litigant in this
case is none other than Issa Ray. She is
the creator of Insecure. It's her tor.
It's clear that she's the boss lady. And
so is Issa Ray tripping for kicking
Amanda Seals out the insecure crew?
>> So just to give my verdict straight out
the gate, no. I don't think Issa Ray is
tripping for kicking Amanda Seals out
the crew.
>> Okay,
>> given all that had happened offcreen,
but I kind of have a different point of
view on why I also think she's not
tripping. Okay. Well, let me render my
snap verdict first. So, my initial
verdict is that Issa Ray is not
tripping. When you're the boss, you get
to call the shots and at the end of what
you want to do.
>> If you want to leave somebody off a bad
and bougie, that's your prerogative to
do. So, I think she's not tripping, but
I'm willing to hear your theory or your
argument in the case as to I don't know
if you're getting to tripping or not
tripping a different way. Well, the
argument that I've been seeing is that
Tiffany's character was pivotal to the
show. There wouldn't have been the
dynamic in the group if it didn't have
Tiffany in it. But I kind of disagree. I
think one of my main issues with
Insecure was the lack of character
development of some of her friends. And
I just really don't feel like they
developed her character to the point
where she needed to be part of reunion
or part of all these extensive
conversations afterwards. I think she
was just comic relief the funny friend.
And I don't blame Amanda Sills and her
acting or anything. I just think her
character really didn't have that much
material to work with.
>> Well, I I feel you when you're saying
that. I would tend to agree with you
that she wasn't so integral in terms of
the actual screen time on the show. Now,
I would argue that Amanda Seals was at
least a little bit more integral in
terms of the promotion of the show, in
terms of bringing eyeballs to the show
because remember she was kind of a big
deal at the time. She was [snorts] one
of the bigger marquee names on the show.
So, even though her character wasn't as
integral as like a Molly or a Lawrence,
I still think that if you go back over
the arc of the show, Amanda Sals herself
was I would consider her an integral
part. Would you agree with that part of
it?
>> I mean, obviously she was integral cuz
she was part of this friend group, but
there were so many story lines with her
where I just wanted to see more of her.
Especially the postpartum depression
episode. I really wanted them to go
deeper into her character and they just
didn't. They just kind of had her pop up
at a hotel waiting to be saved and I was
just kind of disappointed. So, I wanted
her to be integral and I wanted her to
be a bigger deal on the show and she
just wasn't. And I I personally won't be
attending any of the insecure stops,
[laughter]
but you know, I don't think it should be
a big slap in the face to her that she's
not included.
>> Well, I think that it is a slap in the
face that like
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know that it's an unjustifiable
slap in the face because I mean to see
they go on a hate campaign against Isa
Ray. You know what I'm saying? like
she's definitely trashed the [ __ ] out of
Issa Ray for many many years and Isa
hasn't really I feel like she whacked
her once maybe like on the low but I do
feel like it is a snip. I think that
they 100% excluded her because they
don't [ __ ] like her. Now, the reason
why I say not tripping for not [snorts]
liking her is because, well, hey, you
know, when you talk [ __ ] about people,
they may not necessarily want to be
around you.
>> And I can understand that because me and
my partner in crime, Clay Kane, like we
tour together, season, you've been our
right hand on tour. So, you understand
the importance of chemistry when you're
touring, when you're going to different
states together. That's a much different
kind of vibe versus being on set. Maybe
you have scenes together, maybe you
don't. Like we already said, Amanda
didn't really have as many scenes as
other characters did. So, you know, I'm
sure over the years there was tension
there. And even Amanda said she felt
excluded. So, obviously, there was a way
to kind of I don't really like her, so I
ain't gonna really [ __ ] with her. But
when you're on tour, there is an
expectation of there being chemistry on
the stage. If there's like an odd person
out, then that's going to [ __ ] up the
whole flow of the energy and that's not
going to give people what they're there
to see. I don't think that insecure fans
who are buying tickets are there to see
conflict. I think that they're there to
see the camaraderie that people liked
about Insecure.
>> Yeah. And for that matter, I don't think
that it's a bad thing that um Amanda
Sills was left out. I think if anything,
she should be ready to move on from that
part of her life and that project
because like I said, her character was
one-dimensional and undeveloped. So, I
think we should all kind of move on
[laughter]
personally.
>> Well, it seems like Amanda intimated as
such. She made a video of saying, "It's
okay. It's okay." So, maybe that was her
way of saying like, "Yeah, I saw that,
but at the end of the day, I ain't
tripping off of it." So, I guess if
Amanda ain't tripping, if she say that
she ain't tripping off of being death
all bad and bougie, if she ain't
tripping from from being uh not invited,
kicked out the crew, then I guess who
are we to say that they're tripping for
excluding her? So, what's your final
verdict in the case?
>> My final verdict is not tripping. Isa
Ray can do what she want to do.
>> Well, my final verdict is going to be
not tripping. Now, it's a different
reason for not tripping than my initial
verdict. Ultimately, I say not tripping
because you need a report. You need a
great fun environment. That's what the
people want to see. And they're less
likely to get that with Amanda.
>> And that's not me saying that. That's
what Amanda said. Amanda said that there
was some tension there that she wasn't
treated a certain way. So, if they
couldn't treat you like that
>> on set years ago and you've been talking
up now. Yeah.
>> That's not going to be the energy now.
So, the final verdict, not tripping.
Case closed. Okay. The next on the
docket is a case that we're calling get
out of my womb. [laughter]
>> So Tracy Ellis Ross was on Kiki Palmer's
podcast. Ch. She gives us so much
material to work with. I absolutely love
me some Kiki.
>> I need to watch that. I need to watch
her podcast for sure.
>> You know, I need to give her the views
because I see all the repost to all the
Kiki Palmer and stuff. I'm I'm like,
dang, can we get the sister some views
instead of everybody else clipping all
her [ __ ] So, um, we're going to be
guilty of clipping her [ __ ] and posting
it here so that you guys can see exactly
why we're calling this case get out of
my womb.
>> I went through a phase like during
Blackish where I swear to God people
were asking me why I hadn't had children
and had I thought about it. And I
remember saying to one person on camera,
I said, "Will you get out of my womb?"
>> And she was like, "Oh." I said, "No, but
really, like, why are you asking me that
question? That's insane.
>> Oh my god,
>> it actually is insane. [ __ ] why are
you talking to me about what's going on
in my uterus?
>> I know. Oh my god. You know, I've been
there, done that.
>> The charges in this case and Tracy Ellis
Ross is the litigant. Was Tracy Ellis
Ross tripping for telling the
interviewer, "Get out of my womb."
>> My initial verdict is not tripping.
Tracy Ellis Ross was not tripping for
telling people to get up out of her
womb. Leave me in my womb alone, please.
>> Period. I'm going to say my initial
verdict and probably my final verdict is
Tracy Ellis Ross was definitely not
tripping.
>> People need to stop policing and
surveilling the wombs of women. Why do
people feel the need to talk to a
stranger or even a family member about
when they choose or not choose to
reproduce? Now, she did say prior to
this clip that she was asked this
question during interviews while she was
on Blackish, where she plays a mother
and at one point during the show, she
had a brand new baby. So,
[clears throat] I'm not sure if the
questions were that far out of left
field, but just in general, me having
gone through my fertility struggles and
having two kids and just feeling
downright harassed about when you having
kids, why you ain't pregnant, what y'all
doing over there, when y'all having
babies. It's just like part of me feels
like people almost just don't have
anything else to say. Yeah, I think a
lot of these comments come from boredom
and just trying to strike up
conversation, but some of these
[ __ ] do be nosy. And and when
you are able to discern which who's
being nosy and who's just trying to
engage with you, you you definitely can
get out of pocket with them and get away
with it. I'm done.
>> Right. Here's the order of events. When
you're a woman, [laughter]
you spend your whole teenage years
>> trying to not get knocked up and people
threatening, you better not be pregnant.
get pregnant you with pregnancy your
whole [ __ ] teenage years, right? Then
somewhere along the lines, eventually
you get in a relationship, if lucky you
get married, and then they immediately,
instead of threatening you with how you
shouldn't be [ __ ] pregnant, they
start actually harassing you about when
you going to have babies, going to have
baby, when you going to have baby,
>> and don't turn down the liquor or don't
turn down the food you like, oh, you
pregnant
>> or don't actually gain a couple of
pounds and bey
[ __ ] out of here. I remember this one
[ __ ] She sat up there and she asked me
if I was pregnant. I'd already had my
daughter.
>> YOU WERE IN ARUBA.
>> We were in Aruba, [ __ ] And I thought I
[laughter] was looking good. Okay. I had
me a little a little cut out of a
little, you know, a little hair and had
a little cut out on the side.
>> I thought I was high [ __ ] This [ __ ]
gonna ask me, "Oh, oh, something about
you being pregnant, [ __ ] The [ __ ] I'm
not pregnant."
>> So, first of all, I just think that
asking people if they're pregnant is
rude. Okay. A [ __ ] can have a pudge, a
foo or whatever and not be pregnant.
There's that's one. But okay, I I I had
I got a tangent there. So So okay. So
then you get married and they harass you
about when you going to have a kid. Then
if you actually have a kid, what's the
thing?
>> It still don't stop. After you have a
baby, then they like the next one. Yeah,
you have another. You know, they can't
be the only child.
>> Yeah.
>> You ready? You going to try for a boy
now? Like get the [ __ ] out of here.
>> Oh god. Oh god. Yeah. then it's like you
need to get the other gender or you
can't you can't have only [laughter]
child. It never ever ever stops. So I
think that we should normalize telling
people shut the [ __ ] up and stay out of
my womb. And then you also have people
who have experienced pregnancy loss. I
mean people don't understand that 25% of
pregnancies end in miscarriage. So the
odds of you encountering a woman in your
intrusive questions that has had a
miscarriage or had some sort of
pregnancy loss or is having difficulty
conceiving is pretty [ __ ] high. It's
high enough for you to assume that that
is an inappropriate question.
>> Yeah. As a person who has experienced
pregnancy loss several times, that used
to be my favorite go-to line when people
were getting in my business. So, I would
tell them, "Oh, I actually just had a
miscarriage two months ago,
>> the look of shock on people's face." But
hey, you [ __ ] asking, right? So,
right,
>> let's talk about it. I had a
miscarriage. Now what? M
>> so I've been through all that and I feel
Tracy I think that was a very dialed
[snorts] back response to what it could
have been.
>> Well it's definitely dialed back
compared to what my husband said one
time. Now for the record that question
can also be offensive to men. Okay.
>> To me true
>> because one time we were at a family
reunion and one of his uncles mind you
not an uncle that he's like ace bone
cones with or nothing like that. It was
just an uncle who asked my husband in a
group of people, "Where your kids at?"
And he went in these nuts [laughter]
in front of everybody and he was like,
"You should have seen the look of
shock."
>> I know they were shocked.
>> My husband is not the kind of person
who's like a vulgar or who like really
gets all animated like that. He's very
even killed. But that day he had time to
say
>> I need to ask Andrew what his best
response was to someone asking where our
kids was. They probably didn't even ask
his dad. They was too busy harassing me.
>> Yeah. What is your final verdict in the
case of Get Out of My Womb?
>> My final verdict is of course team Tracy
not tripping. Get the [ __ ] out of
people's wombs. Okay. Stop worrying
about what they doing.
>> Absolutely. I second that verdict. My
verdict is also that Tracy is not
tripping. Case closed.
Okay, season. That wraps up our docket
on culture court this week, but we are
rolling on down the courthouse steps to
people's court.
>> People's court is where we take cases
from regular people like us. This week's
people's court case, we're calling it
where my apology at? Where my apology
at? Where my hood at? [laughter]
>> So, let's take a look at a video that I
think will set up this case quite
nicely.
>> And one more thing, please don't start
no small talk with me when you know you
owe me an apology. That's going to piss
me off. Okay? I'm going to need that.
Run me that apology before you come over
here. Okay? Or else you know where you
can go. [laughter]
>> Run me that dog.
>> Yeah. Yes. To some people, apologies are
very important.
>> What's your initial verdict? Was she
tripping? Are are people who need an
apology before proceeding with regular
interactions, are they tripping or not
tripping?
>> Personally, my verdict is she tripping.
You don't need no apology, girl. You
know what this person is up to and how
they act. You can do what you got to do
with that information.
>> Well, my initial verdict is not
tripping. Now, I like to caveat that
because I think my toxic trait, now if
y'all follow me on SiriusXM, then you've
heard me say this before, but my toxic
trait is I don't actually believe in
apologies.
>> Me neither. [laughter] I'm with you.
>> So, for me, I don't care to get an
apology. You don't have to say [ __ ] to
me about apologizing. It's not going to
make me never mind. And you probably
ain't going to get an apology out of me.
The only areas where I apologize is if I
keep you waiting. I hate to keep you
waiting. I hate being late.
If you keep me waiting and you don't
say, "Oh, I'm sorry, girl." We got a
problem. So, that's one area. If I step
on your shoe, I thought there's there's
certain pleasantries where an apology is
required. And you know, it's so funny
because mom really taught us, too. She
was like, "If someone ever tells you
that they hurt your feelings, you should
apologize." And we both was like, "No."
>> How did we have to make sense?
>> I know. We both was like, "Nah, you got
to make some sense if you coming around
with apology. your feelings like
[laughter]
>> I said what I said and I ain't changing
it.
>> Yeah.
>> But why was she tripping? What's wrong
with needing an apology? Even though
we're not trying to
>> already trying to make me change my
verdict, but no. Look, I am
cross-examining you. Okay, I know we're
judges, but you know, look what's going
on. What's T?
>> I mean, honestly, it's going to depend
on what the offense is. She said, don't
come around me talking trying to be
funny. Or she said, what she say? Don't
come around me talking
>> She said, "Don't come around me trying
to be friendly if you know you owe me an
apology." It's I'mma have to see what
What did they do? Like, are you
expecting an apology because they caused
your mama a fat [ __ ] Like, what are
you trying like what happened? Like, you
know, did they talk about your baby
>> or did they keep you waiting or did they
spill your drink? like you know
obviously there's different levels but I
think in general people need to learn
how to operate and maneuver around
people without apologies because
>> it might not even be genuine. So just
get that person out your face. Get the
interaction over with and gone with your
business.
>> Yeah. And see I think that's where my
toxic trait comes in because I'd be like
thinking like you don't even mean that
[ __ ] So what you apologize like you
said what you said you did what you did.
You don't mean it. So what do we what
are we doing? This is like Kabuki
theater at this point again. But I think
it does depend on the severity. I feel
like if somebody is expecting an apology
as a greeting, it must have been
something bad. Like it must have been
some kind of beef there. Maybe somebody
was trashing you behind your back.
Somebody like did something. I don't I
don't feel like somebody says before you
speak to me, you owe me an apology or
nothing.
>> I mean, for me, it's like, oh, so we
cool now?
>> We talking now. We friends. You know,
I'm not going to ask for no apology. I'm
I'm I still hold people accountable
without requiring an apology, you know.
>> So, what does accountability without an
apology look like?
>> For me, accountability without an
apology is both parties expressing how
they feel. Maybe going into their
intentions or whatever, but accepting
that, you know, you did what you did.
You're not really sorry for it. I took
it the way I took it. You can't tell me
how to take it. So, let's just move on.
So, you still want a conversation, but
you just don't necessarily need an
apology.
>> Or you don't need a conversation either.
>> I'm definitely going to bring some [ __ ]
up unless I just really don't give a
[ __ ] about what you did or you.
>> But no, it don't have to be no long
drawn out conversation. It don't have to
be no tears or no paragraphs over text
messages. It's just like, "Hey, I ain't
appreciate that or what was up with
that?" And um if they have something to
say in response to it and don't it
doesn't seem to be heading towards an
apology, then cool.
>> See, I don't even need a conversation or
a confrontation. I just
>> I think the older you get, you kind of
just like, "Okay, girl."
>> I just have always been the kind of
person where it's like I peep game and
that's it. I just I maneuver how I need
to maneuver. I don't make announcements.
It's just like I will switch up on your
ass based on how you have required me to
switch up. It's not going to be
something that I need to articulate. Now
there have been people who have noticed
like oh girl what happened that you was
the only now if you want to ask me. I
ain't going to lie. I ain't going to
gaslight you. I be like I didn't [ __ ]
with how you did XYZ.
>> But I don't really need a conversation.
I don't need apology. I'm team. Oh we
cool? You cool? If you cool I'm cool.
And I let [laughter] people know that if
you not cool, then I'm not going to be
cool cuz we going to not be cool
together. Ain't no way I'm going to be
cool with you when you not cool with me.
That's how that works. Okay.
>> I'm matching energy and all that. But at
my age, I would say I don't require a
conversation probably eight or nine
times out of 10. I'm not arguing with
nobody.
>> I require a conversation zero out of 10.
But let me just tell you before we
render our final verdicts. You know how
you said, "Oh, y'all cool." Now I had a
little messy [ __ ] moment at one of the
concerts because [laughter]
there was a little, you know, kurfuffle
behind me. It was commotion. Now mind
you, I was like, y'all couldn't do all
this [ __ ] when Htown was up there or
still they had to wait till SWB was on
stage and it was all this commotion.
Yes, girl. I was like, I've been waiting
all night for SWB. And so it was all
this commotion behind me and I had to
turn around because you not about to
fall and trip all over me because y'all
tussling. And next thing, you know, I'm
on the ground and I'm on candy camera
because I wasn't paying attention at
all. So I turn around and see what's
going on. So these girls was beefing
beefing beefing beefing beefing because
one chick was just extra excited,
whatever. She was a little sloppy with
it. But barely beefed up. People be
beefed out at concerts.
>> I got into I got into almost artication
too, [ __ ] But that's not the topic
right now. The topic of these other
chicks. So anyh who, so they was beefing
hard, beeping hard, beeping hard.
Security came, but you know they
diffused it. So fast forward, I think
it's about to come on. I hear a little
giggling behind me. So I turn around and
I said, "Oh, y'all made up. Y'all cool
[laughter] down.
>> Were they They didn't know each other."
>> No, they did not know each other. These
are two random chicks who got
>> I love being I love that [ __ ] Yeah. Oh,
so y'all cool. I love it.
>> I said that I couldn't resist cuz it was
a big deal. So when they were I heard a
little kick in behind me. I said, "Oh,
okay. Y'all y'all good now? Y'all made
up?" They didn't even say nothing cuz
you know, look, you know, if you show
your ass that you got to kind of just
So, [laughter]
I'm definitely one. Now, I'm not saying
I'mma look for an apology,
>> but if I see you being cool with
somebody you got into it with, I'm
definitely going to be a messy [ __ ]
You going to be like, "Oh, y'all good.
Y'all cool. Y'all y'all made up."
>> Same. Me, too. You know, I love them
moments.
>> Yes, honey. Okay, so let's render our
final verdict. Season in the case uh
where my apology at are people who
require an apology before proceeding
with cordial interaction tripping or not
tripping? [gasps]
>> My final verdict stands. I think she
tripping. Girl, go move on. Get over it.
These people, they don't care.
>> I'm going to stick with my initial
verdict. My final verdict is not
tripping. If you require an apology,
>> more power to you.
>> More power to you. I ain't going to
judge. I ain't going to hate on
[laughter] you. I ain't going to say
that you emotional and you sensitive. If
you need to suck it up and get over it.
>> I didn't say all that.
>> What?
>> Well, that's what you would say if you
say somebody is tripping because you
emotional or sensitive. Just redirect
your energy and emotions somewhere more
useful. That's what I'm saying.
>> You trying to clean it up, but at the
end cleaning up [ __ ] You don't give a
[ __ ] about apologies, man. Get over that
[ __ ] Listen like Oh, see now you said
get over. That's what I said. You That's
what I said. But that doesn't mean you I
I don't Okay, you right though. No,
you're right. Stand it. Stay in it. You
said I think you should get over it. I
think you shouldn't be running around
waiting for nobody to apologize to you.
>> I hear you on that. Case closed. Okay,
y'all. If you've been enjoying Am I
Tripping so far, you can turn your own
homes into the courtroom by bringing Ami
Tripping home. Go to amit
trippingame.com
and get your own copy today. 180
scenarios to keep the fun and
conversations flowing.
>> Okay.
>> And it's fun. It's fun.
>> It is, if I do say so myself. Okay. So,
the last docket is what we call family
court. That is where season and I put
ourselves on trial. Season, you're the
litigant in this week's family court.
Okay. So, this case is called Kidfree
Family Reunion, and I am the litigate.
>> Okay.
>> My husband's side of the family has a
family reunion in Toronto in a couple of
weeks and we decided to go without our
kids. [laughter]
>> A You said a family reunion. The family
>> reunion. So, the family.
>> It's the family. And
>> the family.
>> And it's crazy because my daughter was
the first girl born in like 20 years.
So,
>> Oh, wow.
>> Yeah. So, people really know and love
our kids,
>> but we need a break, you know. And since
mom is going to be home and said she was
going to miss the kids, we was like,
"Okay, well, we'll just leave them with
you." They had plane tickets and
everything.
>> Oh, you cancelled the plane tickets?
[laughter]
Well, before you get into all of your
initial verdict, my initial verdict,
even though that's my niece and nephew
and I love them down, I'm going to say
not true. That's what my initial ver
initial verdict is. I'm going say I'm
tripping a little bit. Okay. Okay. I
already have this thing called deadbeat
mom tour. My friends named it for me
where I go off for weekends couple times
a year without my husband and my kids.
And at some point that was the only
break I got from my kids. Like my kids
be up my ass and around the corner when
I'm out. I'm surprised I was able to
record this without them up in here.
Uh-huh.
>> So, I already have the Debbie mom tour,
but now that we actually have reliable
child care, my mom is living here now.
Me and Andrew kind of want to get
outside a little bit.
>> But it is a family reunion. And I know
how many people want to see these kids.
>> Yeah.
>> But the trump card is it's Caribana that
we get.
>> Now you really not tripping.
>> So I'm like, how are we going to enjoy
Carabana? which I've been trying to get
to since we moved to Chicago.
>> Oh, yeah. 14.
>> That's on my bucket list, too, for sure.
>> Yeah. So, we had events planned up where
we can bring the kids that were
kid-friendly and when we got the
opportunity to drop them kids, we took
it.
>> Yeah. Well, I think that's fair because
you're going to like kill two [snorts]
birds with one stone. You're going to do
the family reunion, but then you're also
going to do the rest after your friends
at Carabana. I get that part. I think
also because it's international,
traveling with kids, even though it's
Canada, you still need to go through
customs [laughter] and stuff and I don't
been through the Toronto airport. It
ain't no joke. Okay.
>> Traveling with kids anywhere is just
it's a pain in the ass. You just take
>> I think it's more pain for you compared
to me because you have two kids. I only
have one. So my daughter, I ain't got a
problem traveling with her, but for you,
you get a little more stressed out when
you travel.
>> Okay. Yeah, I do. I'm not an airport
warrior. I be stressed out. So, I be
planning everything down to what if they
need this, what if they need that. Like,
yeah,
>> I'mma go to the airport, go to the land
jail, and go sit to our little hopefully
we got first class seats or at least
economy plus. But I will say there is
one thing that you are absolutely
tripping on. Okay.
>> Okay. What is it, girl? Cuz I don't
know.
>> You're tripping because you're going to
miss my show.
>> That is the same day as our one night
only beyond the mic show. It's in DC.
It's our most iconic venue.
>> Look, trust me,
>> you ain't going to be there.
>> I'm devastated about it. I will never
get over the fact that I'm missing your
show. They have been planning this
family reunion for a minute and the
person planning it actually really shows
up for us. So, and of course, I didn't
want to leave my husband hanging with
two kids, but
>> right
>> now the kids ain't gone. So, I'm like,
you know, make the best of it. Make the
best of it. But I am going to hate every
second of this in your show. I know. I
know. But you know [snorts] the world is
bigger than my little show. So I forgive
you. You've been at every show.
>> Good.
>> But you still tripping. Okay.
>> Okay. All right. So you going to get me
tripping or not tripping?
>> To be fair, you are a litigant in this
case for leaving your kids. And that is
not what I say you're tripping on. So my
[laughter] final verdict is that you are
not tripping.
>> Okay. Yay. I don't think I am. So, okay.
My final verdict is I'mma put me first,
Lucious. So, I'm not tripping. I'm
sorry. I got to do what I got to do. And
you know, me and my husband want to see
some mass and titties and, you know, see
rump shaking and I might throw on a
little glitter. You know, you know, and
they your husband Jamaican, too.
>> My husband Jamaican, so he deserves it
and stuff. Yeah, that's true. That's
true.
>> Yeah. The kids will be all right.
>> They'll be all right. Yeah. They will
sometime they will be at home with
Grammy having a good old grand old time.
Okay. So, case closed. Okay, season. And
that does it for all of the cases we
have on the docket. You guys out there
watching, you are the jury. So, it's
time for you to weigh in and deliver
your verdicts on who's tripping or not
tripping. If you want to appeal our
verdicts or if you want to be a litigant
in a future Am I tripping episode, then
you can leave your comments below. You
can contact us through mitrigame.com on
the podcast page and submit your own
case. We know some of you out there are
scandalous and we want to hear about it
and rule on it. Okay? Whether or not you
want to be a litigant, you as a jury
have a very important role because your
likes, your shares, your subscriptions
help us move up in the algorithm. And we
are going to be in the comments
responding to all of your comments. So,
the conversation is not a one-way
street. We're getting right there in the
jury box with you. But for now, that
does it for this week. Court is
adjourned.